# Hamza Qureshi

humzaqureshii98@gmail.com

+92 335 - 2867407

## **About Me**

Hi, My name is Hamza Qureshi and I've been doing SEO since 2020. I start with an off-page. Creating an off-page link building Campaign with unique link opportunities to kick out competitors from the listed target, Can drive leads to sites, guest post outreach, and content sharing on different platforms, and can give you outstanding results in profiles like Reddit, and Quora in 2 months.

# **Positions & Responsibilities**

• Webiz Media PVT LTD (January 2024 - Present)

Sr. SEO (Hamariweb.com)

As a Senior SEO, My responsibilities are

- Developing and implementing SEO strategies to improve website ranking and visibility
- Conducting keyword research and analysis
- Optimizing website content, structure, and architecture
- Staying up-to-date with search engine algorithms and trends
- Collaborating with cross-functional teams (marketing, content, development)

### • InterNative Labs, LLC

SEO Assistant Lead (Feb 2023 - Dec 2023)

Working as SEO Assistant Lead My Duties to manage all search engine optimization and marketing activities. Responsible for managing all SEO activities such as content strategy, Content Audit link building, and keyword strategy to increase rankings on all major search networks.

### Dimension Softwarenz

SEO Executive April 2022 - January 2023

My Duties was to develop link Building Strategy and Work on it, Keep Tracking Keywords Movement, Content Optimization, Disavow toxic backlinks, Competitors Search, Handling Social Media Activities, SMM etc.

## Octopus Tech

Promoted to Junior SEO December 2020 - Feb 2022

Link Building Content Optimization, On-Page & Off-Page Optimization, Keyword Research, Competitor Research, Technical Issues analysis, SEO Plan Suggestions regarding to project needs.

### Education

BBA In (Marketing & Management) From Indus University